Shailesh Kumar

Engineering Student

My abilities like Collaboration and Continuous Learning help me in giving my contributions to the community and I really love to collaborate with amazing people as much as possible so that I can learn from their experiences and pass the same learnings to the community. I'm really good at problem-solving, observation, and communication. I also have leadership skills and therefore I'm an Active Learner who possesses strong Adaptation skills.

GPA: 8.71



- 1429/18, Phase-11, Mohali, SAS Nagar, Mohali, India
- twitter.com/shailesh2002k

- 7589618612
- in linkedin.com/in/shailesh-kumar-27799517a
- github.com/ShaileshKumar007

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology Chandigarh Group of Colleges

08/2020 - Present

Courses

Computer Science

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

Postman Student ExpertPostman

02/2022 - Present

Open Source Contributor EddieHub

10/2021 - Present

Open Source Contributor Web3 Community

10/2021 - Present

Participant HacktoberFest-2021

10/2020 - 11/2020

Achievements/Tasks

- Successfully completed my Hacktoberfest2021
- Done 10+ valid PRs to different Repositories

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Virtual Quiz Game (11/2021 - 12/2021)

 Made a virtual quiz game using OpenCV module in Python. Using computer vision module (i.e. OpenCV) the game will pop up questions on the screen and you have to answer the MCQ question using your hand movements.

Simon Game (02/2022 - 02/2022)

 A game written in JavaScript. This game creates a series of tones and lights and requires a user to repeat the sequence.

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Playing Chess Learning about Astronomy

Reading Books Listening Podcasts

Watching Documentaries Watching Sci-fi Movies

Learning about Ancient History